Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts, 1924-1957 RL.11870
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Contracts for Broadcasting, 1929-1949; undated; 1
  - Shell Oil--Shell Chateau Program, 1935-1937; 62
    - Mario Chamlee, 1937 June 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Marjorie Gateson, 1936 Mar. 21; Oct. 24 (Film-reel 147)
    - Marjorie Lane, 1935 Oct 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Marriage Has Been Arranged--Consent, 1936 Feb. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Martha Raye, 1936 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Martha Sleeper, 1935 June 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Marvin C. Fenstermacher, 1937 May 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mary Ellis, 1936 Apr. 4 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mary Small, 1937 June 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Master of the Revels--Consent, 1935 July 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Max Terr, 1936 Apr. 4; 11 (Film-reel 147)
    - Maxie Rosenbloom, 1935 June 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Maxine Lewis, 1936 Feb. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - May Robson, 1936 Feb. 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - McClallen and Company, 1936 Feb. 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - Melvin Koontz, Olga Celeste, 1936 June 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Merle Oberon, 1936 July 18 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mexican Tipica Orchestra, 1937 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 147)
    - Michael and Mary--Consent, 1935 Sept. 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mickey Rooney, 1935 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Midge Williams, 1936 Jan. 4 (Film-reel 147)
    - Midget act, 1937 May 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mike Riley, Ed Farley, 1936 Feb. 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - Milton Berle, 1935 Oct 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mitzi Green, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Monsieur Beaucaire--Consent, 1936 Jan. 11 (Film-reel 147)
    - Moran and Van, 1935 Dec. 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Jesse Crawford, 1937 June 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Martin Johnson, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mrs. John McGraw, 1937 May 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mrs. Martin Johnson (Osa Johnson), 1937 June 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mrs. Mary Carr, 1935 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mrs. Moonlight--Consent, 1936 Apr. 18 (Film-reel 147)
    - Nadine Connor, 1935 July 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Napoleon's Barber--Consent, 1935 Dec. 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - Nat Holman, 1937 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Nedda Harrigan, 1936 May 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Nick Lucas, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - Niela Goodelle, 1935 Oct 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Nola Day, 1935 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Norman Foster, 1936 May 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Norman Gordon, 1937 May 22; June 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Notre Dame Glee Club, 1937 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Olsen and Johnson, 1936 (Film-reel 147)
    - On the Spot--Consent, 1936 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - One Extra Announcer, 1935 June 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - Original Memphis Five, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Orson Welles, 1937 Apr. 10; June 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Otto Kruger, 1935 June 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Pat O'Brien, 1936 Mar. 28 (Film-reel 147)
    - Patsy Kelly, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 147)
    - Patsy Kelly, 1936 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 151)
      Blurred on reel 147
    - Paul and Jerome Dean, 1935 May 11 (Film-reel 147)
    - Paul Chotteau, 1936 Aug. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Paul Harvey, 1936 Aug. 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - Paul Robeson, 1935 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Paul Taylor and chorus, 1935 Oct. 26; Dec. 21 (Film-reel 147)
    - Peter Ibbetson--Consent, 1936 Aug. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Phillips Holmes, 1935 May 18 (Film-reel 147)
    - Polly Moran, 1935 Apr. 27-29; Nov. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - Putt Mossman, 1936 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ralph Bandini, 1936 Aug. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ralph Forbes, Heather Angel, 1935 Sept. 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ralph Ranger, Leo Robin--Consent, 1936 June 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ray Dooley, 1937 Jan. 9; Feb. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Raymond L. Ditmars, 1937 June 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Red McKenzie and His Mound City Blowers, 1937 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 147)
    - Reed Kennedy, 1935 Oct 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Reflected Glory--Consent, 1936 Aug. 22; Sept. 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Rev. Bernard R. Hubbard, 1937 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ricardo Cortez, 1936 July 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Richard Bartholomess, 1935 July 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Richard Kollmar, 1937 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Risin' Waters--Consent, 1937 May 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Robert McWade, 1935 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Robert Porterfield, 1937 May 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Robert Wildhack, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 147)
    - Roger Pryor, 1936 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Roscoe Ates, 1935 Aug. 24 (Film-reel 147)
    - Roscoe Turner, 1935 Aug. 24 (Film-reel 147)
    - Rose Bampton, 1937 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Rosenbloom and Morrison, 1935 June 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ross Gorman and quintet, 1937 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Roy Atwell, 1937 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Roy Hallee, 1937 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Rube Goldberg, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Rufe Davis, 1937 May 29; June 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Russian Balalaika Orchestra, 1937 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ruth Chatterton, 1935 July 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sailors Octet, 1935 Nov. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sally Rand, 1936 June 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sam Coslow, 1935 Aug. 10 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sam Hermann, 1937 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sam Parks Jr., 1935 June 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - Scotty Noble, 1936 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 147)
    - Shaw and Lee, 1935 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sheila Barrett, 1935 May 11; 1936 May 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Shining Hour--Consent, 1936 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sidney Jervis, 1935 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sidney Reiss, 1937 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sigmund Spaeth, 1935 Nov. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Small Miracle--Consent, 1935 July 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Smith Ballew, 1936 Apr. 4-Sept. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Snowy Baker, 1936 July 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sonja Henie, 1936 May 2; 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sophie Tucker, 1935 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Spencer Tracy, 1936 May 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Spring--Consent, 1936 Mar. 28 (Film-reel 147)
    - Stanley Morner, 1935 Dec. 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - Stepin Fetchit, 1937 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sterling Holloway, 1936 Mar. 28 (Film-reel 147)
    - Stoopnagle and Budd, 1937 May 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Suzanna Fischer, 1937 Feb. 20; Mar. 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Swedish Bell Ringers, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Swore and Good, 1935 June 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sylvia Froos, 1935 June 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Tallulah Bankhead, 1936 Aug. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Taxi in the Rain--Consent, 1935 Nov. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Teddy Bergman, 1937 May 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Texas Mustang Band, 1935 Dec. 28 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Bad Man--Consent, 1935 Nov. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Barker--Consent, 1935 June 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Big House--Consent, 1935 Oct. 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Bishop's Candlesticks--Consent, 1937 May 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Bride the Sun Shines On--Consent, 1935 Sept. 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Cavaliers, 1937 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Champ--Consent, 1935 Oct. 25; Dec. 28 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Constant Nymph--Consent, 1936 Aug. 8; Sept. 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Copperhead--Consent, 1935 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Dove--Consent, 1935 May 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Finger Man--Consent, 1936 July 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Five Cabin Kids, 1937 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Frim Sisters, 1935 Oct 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Front Page--Consent, 1935 June 29; 1936 June 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Green Goddess--Consent, 1935 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Jest--Consent, 1935 Apr. 27-29 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Lake--Consent, 1935 July 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Last Mile--Consent, 1935 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Old Soak--Consent, 1935 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Racket--Consent, 1936 Apr. 11 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Southernaires Quartet, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Swan--Consent, 1935 May 11 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Three DeMarcos, 1937 May 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Three Marshalls, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Truth About the Blayds--Consent, 1936 Mar. 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Valiant--Consent, 1935 Nov. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Vass Children, 1937 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Watson Sisters, 1935 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 147)
    - There's Always Juliet--Consent, 1936 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - They Knew What They Wanted--Consent, 1936 May 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Thomas Carr, 1935 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Tim Ryan, Irene Noblette, 1935 Dec. 28 (Film-reel 147)
    - Tony Bond, 1936 Aug. 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - Tony Canzonari, 1935 June 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - Toscha Seidel, 1937 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Toto, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Toya Sasabe, 1937 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 147)
    - Treasure Island--Consent, 1935 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Two Men Met at the Vesle--Consent, 1935 Nov. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ty Cobb, 1936 May 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Una Merkel, 1936 Feb. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Use of assumed name "Peggy Gardiner" from Nadine Connor--Consent, 1935 July 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Use of name "Peggy Gardiner"--Consent, 1935 Oct 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Valley Forge--Consent, 1936 Feb. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Vance Breese, 1935 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Vera Van, 1936 Apr. 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Vi Bradley, 1936 Mar. 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - Victor Moore, 1936 Apr. 11 (Film-reel 147)
    - Victor Young's Orchestra, 1935 Apr. 6-1936 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Vienna Boys Choir, 1937 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Virginia Bruce, 1936 May 9; Aug. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Viva Villa--Consent, 1935 Oct 12; 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - W.A. Coates, 1937 May 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - W.S. Van Dyke, 1935 Nov. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walker Cochran, 1936 June 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Wallace Beery, 1935 Oct. 12-Dec. 28 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walter Connolly, 1936 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walter Hagen, 1936 Jan. 4 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walter Hampden, 1935 May 25; 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walter Huston, 1935 June 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walter O'Keefe, 1937 June 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walter Winchell, 1936 June 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - War Brides--Consent, 1935 June 15; 1937 May 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Warden Lewis E. Lawes, 1937 June 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Warren Williams, 1936 May 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - William Lynn, 1937 Mar. 13; June 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - William Moran, 1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - William Reeve, 1935 June 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - William Tilden, 1935 Nov. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Willie Howard, 1935 July 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Willie Saunders, 1935 May 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Within the Law--Consent, 1935 July 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Worthington Minor, 1937 June 19 (Film-reel 147)
    - Yacht Club Boys, 1936 Jan. 4; Apr. 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - You and I--Consent, 1936 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Young Woodley--Consent, 1935 May 18 (Film-reel 147)
    - Zazu Pitts, 1936 May 23 (Film-reel 147)
  - Standard Brands, 1936; 63
    - Widlar Products, 1936 Apr. 3-Dec. 25 (Film-reel 145)
  - Standard Brands--Chase & Sanborn, 1937; 64
    - Betty Janes, 1937 May 9 (Film-reel 145)
    - Clark Gable, 1937 Aug. 26 (Film-reel 160)
  - Standard Brands--Chase & Sanborn--Coffee Hour, 1937-1941; 65
    - A Cup of Tea--Consent, 1937 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 145)
    - A Kiss for Cinderella--Consent, 1937 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 145)
    - A Little Game--Consent, 1939 July 2 (Film-reel 145)
    - A Marriage Has Been Arranged--Consent, 1939 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 145)
    - A Swell Night--Consent, 1937 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - A Wedding--Consent, 1937 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - Accent on Youth--Consent, 1938 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - After the Party's Over--Consent, 1939 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Akim Tamiroff, 1939 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 145)
    - Alan Marshall, 1939 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Alan Mowbray, 1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Alec Templeton, 1939 June 11; 18; 25 (Film-reel 145)
    - Alexander's Horse--Consent, 1938 July 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Alice Brady, 1937 Aug. 15; 1938 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 145)
    - Alice Fay, 1938 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 145)
    - All Quiet on the Western Front--Consent, 1937 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Andrea Leeds, 1937 Nov. 28; 1939 July 16 (Film-reel 145)
    - Angels Don't Marry--Consent, 1938 Dec. 18 (Film-reel 145)
    - Anita Louise, 1939 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 145)
    - Ann Sothern, 1937 July 18; 1940-1941 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Anna Christie--Consent, 1937 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 145)
    - Anna May Wong, 1938 Nov. 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - Anna Neagle, 1937 Nov. 14; 1940 June 16 (Film-reel 145)
    - Annabella, 1939 June 4 (Film-reel 145)
      Stage name of French actress Suzanne Georgette Charpentier (1907-1996)
    - Arlene Harris, 1940 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Arrowsmith--Consent, 1938 Nov. 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - Arthur Treacher, 1939 Dec. 3; 1940 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 145)
    - Attila Baggio, 1937 July 18 (Film-reel 145)
    - Balcony Scene--Consent, 1939 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 145)
    - Barbara Jo Allen, 1939-1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Barbara Stanwyck, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Basil Fomeen, 1940 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 145)
    - Basil Rathbone, 1938 July 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Beatrice Fairfax, 1939 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Beatrice Lillie, 1937 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 145)
    - Before Dawn--Consent, 1939 June 11 (Film-reel 145)
    - Before the Curtain Rises--Consent, 1938 July 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Bette Davis, 1937 Sept. 12; 1938 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Beulah Bondi, 1938 Aug. 14 (Film-reel 145)
    - Billie Burke, 1937 Nov. 21; 1940 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Billy Burke, 1937 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 146)
    - Billy Gilbert, 1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Billy Lenhar and Kenneth Brown, 1940 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 145)
    - Billy Mauch, 1937 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Bob Burns, 1938 May 15 (Film-reel 145)
    - Bob O'Brien, Ray Gilbert, 1941 Apr. 27 (Film-reel 145)
    - Borderline--Consent, 1938 Dec. 25 (Film-reel 145)
    - Boris Karloff, 1938 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 145)
    - Brains--Consent, 1937 Oct. 31 (Film-reel 145)
    - Brenda--Consent, 1939 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Brock Pemberton--Personal appearance consent, 1937 July 11 (Film-reel 145)
    - Bruna Castagha, 1937 Aug. 1 (Film-reel 145)
    - Candle Light--Consent, 1937 June 6 (Film-reel 145)
    - Carmela--Consent, 1938 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 145)
    - Carmen Miranda, 1941 (Film-reel 145)
    - Carole Lombard, 1937-1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Catherine Parr, 1938 July 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Cecil B. DeMille, 1941 Apr. 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - Charles Boyer, 1941 Mar. 9 (Film-reel 145)
    - Charles Irwin, 1939 July 16; Aug. 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - Charles Judels, 1940 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - Charles Laughton, 1939-1941 (Film-reel 145)
    - Charles Laughton, 1941 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 146)
    - Chester Morris, 1941 Apr. 27 (Film-reel 145)
    - Chester Morris, 1941 Oct. 12 (Film-reel 146)
    - Christmas Prayer--Consent, 1938 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 145)
    - Clarence Nash, 1941 June 1 (Film-reel 145)
    - Clark Gable, 1937-1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Claudette Colbert, 1937-1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Cliff Nazarro, 1939 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 145)
    - Consent from JWT for Margaret English for Sweet Sorrow, 1940 June 2 (Film-reel 145)
    - Consent from JWT for Young & Rubicam to use Edgar Bergen's name, 1939 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Constance Bennett, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Coquette--Consent, 1938 Nov. 6 (Film-reel 145)
    - Country Doctor--Consent, 1938 May 22 (Film-reel 145)
    - Courage ala Carte--Consent, 1939 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Cradle Snatchers--Consent, 1937 May 23 (Film-reel 145)
    - Dale Carnegie, 1941 Oct. 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dark Victory--Consent, 1937 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 145)
    - Dave Rubinoff, 1937 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 145)
    - David Niven, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Deanna Durbin, 1940 Apr. 7; Sept. 1 (Film-reel 145)
    - Deanna Durbin, 1941 Sept. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dear Anne--Consent, 1939 July 16 (Film-reel 145)
    - Death of a Lady--Consent, 1937 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 145)
    - Designing Women--Consent, 1939 July 30 (Film-reel 145)
    - Doc Rockwell, 1940 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Dodsworth--Consent, 1938 July 31 (Film-reel 145)
    - Don Ameche, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Donald Crisp, 1937 Oct. 31 (Film-reel 145)
    - Donald Dickson, 1937-1941 (Film-reel 145)
    - Door of Opportunity--Consent, 1939 Oct. 15 (Film-reel 145)
    - Dorothy Lamour, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Dr. Allan Roy Defoe, 1940 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 145)
    - Dr. Irving P. Krick, 1940 June 23 (Film-reel 145)
    - Dub Taylor, 1940 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Eddie Bracken, 1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1938 Jan. 2-July 1 (Film-reel 145)
    - Edgar Kennedy, 1940 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - Edna Mae Oliver, 1941 May 25 (Film-reel 145)
    - Edward Arnold, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Edward Everett Horton, 1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Eileen Monte, Betty Brewer, Colleen Collins, 1941 Apr. 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - Elizabeth the Queen--Consent, 1938 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 145)
    - Ella Logan, 1938 Aug. 14 (Film-reel 145)
    - Emperor Jones--Consent, 1937 May 23 (Film-reel 145)
    - Enchanted Cottage--Consent, 1937 July 18 (Film-reel 145)
    - Eric Blore, 1939 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Errol Flynn, 1938 Sept. 11; 1940 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - Estimates and costs, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Exact Science of Matrimony--Consent, 1938 June 5 (Film-reel 145)
    - Family Album--Consent, 1939 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Fancy Meeting You Here--Consent, 1939 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 145)
    - Fantasy in Spring--Consent, 1939 June 4 (Film-reel 145)
    - Farewell to Love--Consent, 1937 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Fay Bainter, 1938 Aug. 31; 1939 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 145)
    - Fay Wray, 1939 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Fifty Roads to Town--Consent, 1937 July 18 (Film-reel 145)
    - Five Star Finale--Consent, 1938 July 24 (Film-reel 145)
    - Florence Gill, 1940 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Folios, 1941 July-Aug. (Film-reel 145)
    - For I Am Yours--Consent, 1939 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Forman Brown, 1941 Mar. 16; 23 (Film-reel 145)
    - Frank B. Gompert, 1940 May 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Frank Buck, 1939 Jan. 22 (Film-reel 145)
    - Frank Morgan, 1940 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 145)
    - Franklin Pangborn, 1941 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Fred MacMurray, 1938 Mar. 20; 1939 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - French Leave--Consent, 1938 June 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Gene Autry, 1938 Sept. 18 (Film-reel 145)
    - Gene Lockhart, 1939 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 145)
    - Gene Tierney, 1941 Nov. 15; 23 (Film-reel 146)
    - George Brent, 1939 May 28 (Film-reel 145)
    - Geraldine Fitzgerald, 1939 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Ginger Rogers, 1937; 1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Gladys George, 1937 July 11; 1938 May 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - Gladys Swarthout, 1938 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - Glenda Farrell, 1937 Aug. 22 (Film-reel 145)
    - Gloria Jean--Consent, 1939 Dec. 24; 1940 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 145)
    - Good Fishing--Consent, 1938 Aug. 21 (Film-reel 145)
    - Goodnight, Please--Consent, 1938 Sept. 11 (Film-reel 145)
    - Graham McNamee, 1938; 1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Grammar Sequences--Consent, correspondence, folios, 1938 Mar. 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - Greasy Luck--Consent, 1937 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 145)
    - Grisha Goluboff, 1937 June 20 (Film-reel 145)
    - He Caught a Tartar--Consent, 1939 Feb. 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Hedda Hopper, 1941 Oct. 26; Nov. 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Hedy Lamarr, 1941 Nov. 30 (Film-reel 146)
    - Helen Broderick, 1939 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Helen Hayes, 1939 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Henry Fonda, 1938 Nov. 27 (Film-reel 145)
    - Herbert Marshall, 1937 Sept. 19; 26 (Film-reel 145)
    - Hoagy Carmichael, 1937 July 4 (Film-reel 145)
    - Holiday--Consent, 1938 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 145)
    - Hometown--Consent, 1939 Aug. 6 (Film-reel 145)
    - Hop-O'-Me-Thumb--Consent, 1937 July 4 (Film-reel 145)
    - Humphrey Bogart, 1939 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 145)
    - I Love an Actress--Consent, 1938 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 145)
    - Ida Lupino, 1937-1941 (Film-reel 145)
    - Ideal Man--Consent, 1939 May 21 (Film-reel 145)
    - If at First You Don't Succeed--Consent, 1939 July 9 (Film-reel 145)
    - Ile--Consent, 1938 May 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - In the Dark--Consent, 1937 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 145)
    - Incident at Midnight--Consent, 1939 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 145)
    - Irene Ryan, 1940 Dec. 1 (Film-reel 145)
    - Irving S. Cobb, 1940 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - Jack Oakie, 1939; 1941 (Film-reel 145)
    - Jackie Cooper, 1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Jamaica Inn--Consent, 1939 Oct. 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - James Cagney, 1940 June 9 (Film-reel 145)
    - James Hilton, 1941 Dec. 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - James Stewart, 1941 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 145)
    - Jean Arthur, 1938 Nov. 6; 1939 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Jeannette McDonald, 1940 May 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Jest of Hahalaba--Consent, 1938 Dec. 11 (Film-reel 145)
    - Joan Bennett, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Joe Bigelow's comedy material--Consent, 1939 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 145)
    - John Barrymore, 1938 Aug. 7; 1940 Sept. 22 (Film-reel 145)
    - John Carter, 1938 Feb. 8-MaY 1 (Film-reel 145)
    - John Garfield, 1939 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Jon Hall, 1937 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 145)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1937 May 30; 1940 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 145)
    - Joseph Bentonelli, 1937 May 16 (Film-reel 145)
    - Josephine Hutchinson, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Josephine Sitjar, 1940 June 2 (Film-reel 145)
    - Judge LeRoy Dawson, 1940 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 145)
    - Judith Anderson, 1938 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 145)
    - Judy Garland, 1940 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Judy Garland, 1941 Sept. 7; Dec. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Judy, Zeke, Annie Canova, 1938 (Film-reel 145)
    - June Duprez, 1940 May 5 (Film-reel 145)
    - June Preisser, 1940 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Kathryn Grayson, 1941 Feb. 9; 15 (Film-reel 145)
    - Kay Francis, 1939 Jan. 8; July 30 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lacrymosa--Consent, 1938 Apr. 10 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lana Turner, 1941 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lana Turner, 1941 Dec. 14 (Film-reel 146)
    - Lansing Hatfield, 1939-1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Laurence Olivier, 1940 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lauritz Melchior, 1935 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 145)
    - Let Us Be Gay--Consent, 1938 Sept. 25 (Film-reel 145)
    - Londonderry Air--Consent, 1937 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 145)
    - Loretta Lee, 1938 Jan. 9; Aug. 7 (Film-reel 145)
    - Loretta Young, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lou Gehrig, 1940 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lovely Miracle--Consent, 1938 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lucille Ball, 1941 Mar. 2; June 22 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lucky Day--Consent, 1937 Aug. 22 (Film-reel 145)
    - Luis Alberni, 1939 July 30 (Film-reel 145)
    - Luise Squire, 1938 Mar. 8 (Film-reel 145)
    - Lupe Velez, 1938 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 145)
    - Madeleine Carroll, 1938-1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Madge Evans, 1937 Sept. 19; 1938 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 145)
    - Mae West, 1937 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 145)
    - Magnificent Obsession--Consent, 1938 May 29 (Film-reel 145)
    - Magnolias Have Thorns--Consent, 1939 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 145)
    - Man Mountain Dean, 1940 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 145)
      Ring name of Frank Simmons Leavitt (18991-1953), professional wrestler
    - Man's Best Friend--Consent, 1939 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 145)
    - Margaret Sullivan, 1938 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 145)
    - Margo, 1938 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 145)
    - Marlene Dietrich, 1938-1940 (Film-reel 145)
    - Marlene Dietrich, 1941 Oct. 19 (Film-reel 146)
    - Marli Shiler, 1941 (Film-reel 145)
    - Martha Raye, 1941 May 11 (Film-reel 145)
    - Mary Lee, 1939 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 145)
    - Mary of Scotland--Consent, 1938 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 145)